011networks.com 2006-12-18

# Privacy Policy for 011 Networks

** 011 Networks **

** PRIVACY POLICY**

1) **Privacy Commitment.**

a) 011 Networks. ("011 Networks") is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to its Web sites ("Sites"). To accomplish this, 011 Networks has implemented a comprehensive Online Privacy Policy that governs all information collected on or submitted to 011 Networks' Sites. This Online Privacy Policy is available by links located on 011 Networks homepage and at every point where personal information may be requested. 

b) Any person accessing, browsing, or otherwise using, either manually or via an automated device or program, to the extent permitted hereunder, is a "User" for purposes of this Online Privacy Policy and may be referred to as "User," "Users" or "You" in this Online Privacy Policy. You are bound by the terms of this Online Privacy Policy. By accessing, browsing or using any of 011 Networks' Sites, You acknowledge that You have read, understand, and agree to the terms and conditions of this Online Privacy Policy. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED AND/OR DO NOT AGREE TO THE PROVISIONS OF THIS ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AND ALL OF ITS PROVISIONS, YOUR SOLE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE YOUR USE OF THIS SITE.

c) 011 Networks operates in some countries that have implemented data privacy laws and in others that do not have such laws regarding the processing of Personal Information (defined below). 011 Networks endeavors to protect Users' Personal Information according to the world's most rigorous standards which are set forth in the European Union ("EU") Data Protection Directive. The EU directive establishes common rules to safeguard the fundamental rights and freedoms of individuals in respect of personal data.

d) To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, 011 Networks has put in place what 011 Networks believes are commercially reasonable and sufficient physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information 011 Networks collects through its Sites, including Personal Information. However, 011 Networks cannot guarantee and has no control over the public, in certain cases, or third party network through which You may send Personal Information to 011 Networks' Sites.

e) This Online Privacy Policy is subject to change. Any changes to 011 Networks' Online Privacy Policy will be posted on this Site. All information submitted through 011 Networks' Sites to 011 Networks is subject to the terms and conditions of this Online Privacy Policy, as amended. This Online Privacy Policy was last updated on November 14, 2001.

2) **Information Which May Be Collected and How It May Be Used.**

a) Non-Personal and Aggregated Information Collected Automatically. When You visit 011 Networks' Site, 011 Networks may log general data, such as Your domain name (e.g., 011 Networks.com), the name of the Web page from which You entered 011 Networks Site, which pages You visit on 011 Networks Site, and how much time You spend on each page. We may use this information to continually monitor and improve 011 Networks Site and for internal analyses. We may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track Users' movement, and gather information for aggregate use.

b) Submission of Personal Details. 011 Networks collects information which Users may submit to 011 Networks on a form such as name, address, telephone number, email address, and other information ("Personal Information"). Any Personal Information You submit on this Site will be treated and processed by 011 Networks only in accordance with this Online Privacy Policy. Any time You submit personal information for a specific purpose using the Site, Your information is used for that purpose only, unless You consent otherwise or as required by law. By submitting any Personal Information on this Site, You consent to 011 Networks holding and processing that information, both electronically and manually, and You also consent to the transfer, storage and processing of such data between 011 Networks' offices worldwide. You understand and agree that other countries may not provide privacy protections similar to those Your country provides.

c) Cookies. The term "cookie" refers to files that are transferred from a Web site to Your computer's hard drive. See http://www.cookiecentral.com for information about cookies.

i) Some (usually newer) versions of Web browsers allow You to decide whether or not to accept cookies and some programs notify You when a Web site is about to deposit a cookie on Your hard drive. If You decide not to accept cookies, You may not be able to successfully navigate some portions of 011 Networks' Sites.

ii) 011 Networks may use cookies for the customized presentation of Web pages. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from Your computer that was not originally sent in the cookie, nor does 011 Networks use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, except as expressly set forth in this Online Privacy Policy or as You may otherwise agree.

3) **Sharing Information.**

a) Unless 011 Networks has Your permission or is required by law, 011 Networks only shares the personal information You provide through 011 Networks' Sites with 011 Networks' affiliates and/or business partners that are acting on 011 Networks' behalf. 011 Networks makes every reasonable effort to ensure that such 011 Networks affiliates and business partners, including those in the U.S. and/or any other countries, protect Your personal information consistent with this Online Privacy Policy.

b) We may share non-personal, aggregated information with 011 Networks customers, partners, and advertisers. Aggregated information is not linked to any personal information that can identify an individual person.

4) **Children's Privacy Commitment.**

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, no part of 011 Networks' Sites are structured to attract anyone under 13 and 011 Networks abides by the United States' Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) requirements and does not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from children under the age of 13.

5) **Opt Out Policy.**

You may request not to be contacted by 011 Networks in connection with any new services, updates, promotions, news, or system outages. Such "opt out" requests should be sent to the address indicated on any such material or by replying to such material.

6) **Linked Internet Web Sites.**

011 Networks' Sites may provide hyperlinks which, when clicked, take You to another place within the document, to another document altogether, or to other Web sites not controlled by 011 Networks. These hyper-linked Web sites may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided herein. 011 Networks is not responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of information collected through these Web sites.

7) **Correcting, Amending, or Deleting User Information.**

011 Networks honors requests from You to correct, amend, or delete Your account information (for example, Your name, address, or billing information). You may verify that appropriate corrections have been made. To correct, amend or delete account information, click [here](mailto:Sales@011Networks.com). To protect Your privacy and security, 011 Networks will also take reasonable steps to verify Your identity before granting access or making corrections.

** Contacting 011 Networks:**

If You have any questions about this Online Privacy Policy, the practices of 011 Networks' Sites, or Your dealings with this Site, You can contact: 

011 Networks, L.L.C.

P.O. Box 1382

O'Fallon, MO  63366

(636) 794-6181

Copyright 2004 - 011 Networks  

**Home**
